clanwebsite.com 2014-05-24

# Website Privacy Policy

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

This document represents a legal document that serves as our Privacy Policy. It governs the privacy terms of our Website and Services.   Our Privacy Policy is part of our Legal Terms. Capitalized terms, unless otherwise defined below, have the meaning specified within our Terms of Service.

The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on March 7, 2013.   

#### ** **

### Your Privacy

###### **iClan Websites** follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy.  Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. 

We break up the types of information you share into Non Personal Information and Personally Identifiable Information.

"Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser. 

"Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within access to certain features of our Website.  Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your email address, physical location, business name, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.  It may also include payment information for Services any content you that upload our Services.

### Information We Collect

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to **iClan Websites** when using our Website.

As a visitor, you can browse our Website to find out more about us and our Services.  You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a visitor.

However, if you register an Account with our Website, you must provide Personally Identifiable Information to **iClan Websites** in order for us to provide you with our Services.   We collect your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways: 

####  

#### At Account Registration

When you register for an Account, you will provide us with name, location, email, and payment information. 

####  

#### Using our Services

By using our Services, you can upload content to your Website.    However, your website content is NOT subject to our Privacy Policy. 

####  

#### Online Forms

There may be online forms used in our Website.  The information you enter into these online forms may contain Personally Identifiable Information. 

### Computer Information Collected

When you use our Service, **iClan Websites** **** automatically collects certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website.  Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information.  **iClan Websites** **** also collects the following:

#### Cookies

Our Services uses “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited.  A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser.  We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website.  Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies.  However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all.  We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

####  

#### Web Beacons 

We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails.  Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website.  We do not link Non Personal Information from Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.

####  

#### Automatic Information

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device.  This information includes the name of the Website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the Website to which you’re headed when you leave our Website.  This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system.  We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website. 

#### Payment Details

We do not store any credit/debit card details. All payment processing is carried out using a 3rd party using the strictest protection and encryption standards. We will however store information such as time and date of payment, your billing address and your name.

### How We Use Your Information

**iClan Websites** uses the information we receive from you as follows:

####  

#### Providing and Improving Our Service

**iClan Websites** may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to provide our Website and Services to you as well as to make improvements to them.

#### Communications and Email Alerts

When **iClan Websites** communicates with you about our Website, we will use the email address you provided when registering as a Member.  We may also send you Website alerts regarding your use of our Service.  Finally, we may also send you emails with promotional information about **iClan Websites** , unless you have opted out of receiving such information.  You can change contact preferences at any time through your account.  While you can opt-out of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving Website alerts.

#### Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties

**iClan Websites** does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes.  However, we may use demographic information for data aggregation purposes which might be sold to other parties at our discretion.  Any such data aggregation would not contain any of your Personally Identifiable Information.  We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide Websites to **iClan Websites** with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, webhosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective Websites and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information. 

#### Community Discussion Boards

Our Website may offer the capability for Users to communicate with each other through online Community Discussion Boards.  **iClan Websites** does not filter or monitor what is posted on such discussion boards.  If you chose to post on these discussion boards, you should use care when exposing any Personally Identifiable Information as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information through such postings.

#### Legally Required Releases of Information

**iClan Websites** may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of **iClan Websites** , our Users, employees, and affiliates.

#### Disclosures to Successors

If **iClan Websites** is acquired or merges, in whole or in part, with another business that would become responsible for providing the Service to you, we retain the right to transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to the new business.  The new business would retain the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by the new business. 

###  

### Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties

We believe in everyone’s right to privacy.  If any content you upload to your website contains the images of third parties (i.e. bystanders), you need to make sure you have permission to include them in your content.  While we are not legally liable for the actions of our users, we will remove any images for which we are notified that such images violate the privacy rights of others.

### Privacy Settings

Your Account comes with privacy settings, which allows you to hide certain Personally Identifiable Information such as your email address and age. If you choose to show Personally Identifiable Information in your Account you accept full responsibility for any further consequences. Also, please note that Administrators will still have access to all of your Account information.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites.  You agree that **iClan Websites** has no control over such websites and that such websites are NOT subject to this Privacy Policy.  These websites may have their own privacy policies and other legal documents.  It is your sole responsibility to verify the privacy policies and other legal documents of such websites to see how they treat your personal information. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk.  

###  

### Our Email Policy

**iClan Websites** and our affiliates fully comply with international laws regarding SPAM.  You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from **iClan Websites** and/or our affiliates.  We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission. 

### Our Security Policy

**iClan Websites** has constructed our Service with security in mind. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot completely guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely protected.  We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and to not share it with anyone.  You should always log out of our Website when not in use, especially if you are sharing a computer or mobile device with someone else or are using a public computer.

### Privacy Policy Updates

**iClan Websites** reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.  Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies. 

### Changing Your Information

You may change your email address or other Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the Account management features found on our Website.
